hi there! with Nova Imago
you can get professional headshots in just 30 minutes
let me show you how it works
go to the dashboard and select train a model
fill in the form
and select the options that describe you best
like gender ethnicity,
hair colour, eye colour
maybe you wear glasses or maybe you're bald
then continue to upload your selfies
first read the tips carefully to get the best results
upload your photos
you can add or remove pictures anytime
and then start the AI training
during the training you can leave this page
we'll send you an email as soon as it's finished
once the training is done
you can generate your photos
choose the styles you want and then click continue
here you can pick the format
you'll also see how many pictures you will generate
and how many credits it will take
when your professional headshots are ready
you'll find them in your gallery
just select the ones you like
and download them to your device. thank you for watching!